# ERIK PROENÇA

Full Stack Developer erik@erikproenca.me +55 11 9 8616-5932

#### **PROFILE:**

I am a mathematician, husband and father. I worked as a teacher for 14 years and in 2020 I made the decision to switch to the programming area, which has always been a great passion of mine. Currently I work as a Full Stack developer and also as a programming instructor. I work with several tools, including MuleSoft, React, FastAPI, Dynamics 365. I love solving challenges and puzzles.

#### **EDUCATION:**

Bacharel of Science. Major in Mathematics and minor in Physics.

Anhanguera 2007-2009

Full Stack Developer

Impacta 2021-2021

#### **SKILLS:**

- · JavaScript
- · MuleSoft
- · Python
- · FastAPI
- · Dynamics 365

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

# MULESOFT DEVELOPER

From 06/2022 | ORANGE DOOR IT

Work as a team, developing solutions to meet customer needs, build and maintain api, support customer, testes APIs, build architectures, communicate with SalesForce. Languages developing: Java.

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

From 06/2020 to 02/2023| Erik Proença

Develop end-to-end applications using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript || React on the frontend and using FastAPI, or NodeJS as middleware and MongoDB, or SQL, or MySQL as database. Work as a team, developing solutions to meet customer needs and demands focused on the ERP area. Know how to work with agile methodologies, code versioning and repositories. Test and identify possible problems.

#### **DYNAMICS 365 DEVELOPER**

From 10/2021 to 06/2022 | Nexer

Work as a team, developing solutions to meet customer needs and demands focused on the ERP area. Know how to work with agile methodologies, code versioning and repositories. Test and identify possible problems. Languages developing: AL, C#(.Net)

# PROGRAMMING INSTRUCTOR I

From 09/2021 to 06/2022 | Impacta

Teach: Logic, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Angular Instruct students to understand problems and build solutions.

#### PROGRAMMING INSTRUCTOR II

From 01/2022 to 06/2022 | FIAP

Couch trainees at Projeto Decola Tech Teach HTML, CSS & JS teach Nodejs and mentor students

#### **CERTIFICATES:**

Impacta Certificates

Programming Logic Concepts with JavaScript (2021)

Completed the training of Programming Logic Concepts with JavaScript - 20 hours. period from 05/03/2021 to 05/07/2021

Front End Development with HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript

Completed Front End Development training with HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript - 60 hours period from 05/10/2021 to 05/28/2021

**Data Technologies** 

Completed data technology training (Online - Live) - 32 hours period from 05/31/2021 to 06/10/2021

Front End Node.JS

Completed Front End Node training. JS - 52 hours period from 07/01/2021 to 07/20/2021

Front End Development with React, Angular and TypeScript

Completed Front End Development training with React, Angular and TypeScript - 100 hours period from 07/21/2021 to 08/20/2021

#### **LANGUAGES:**

- · Portuguese
- · English
- · French

# **INTERESTS:**

Family

Trips

Games